Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Colleges and Universities - Fairmont School and Junior College - Fairmont School and Junior College, ca. 1930 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  numbers indicate that copy negatives were created and are filed with those from the Historic Image Collection
- Colleges and Universities - Gallaudet University - Gallaudet University, 1884-1964 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University - Centennial, 1889 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University - Commencement, 1884-1947 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University - Medical Department, 1883 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  2 copies of Pamphlet
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University - Programs, 1904-1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University - Sesquicentennial, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Colleges and Universities - Georgetown University - "Visiting Georgetown University in the Mid-Twenthieth Century", ca. 1965 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - George Wasington University, 1912-1962 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Annual Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Art Exhibits, 1950-1953 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Building Dedications, 1924-1940 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Bulletins, 1904-1925 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Commencement, 1910-1941 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Congressional Reports, 1910-1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Reference the Murrill Act and an investigation
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Convocations, 1929-1956 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Fund Raising, 1907-1924 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Inauguration of President, 1961-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Lectures and Discussions, 1937-1948 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Performance Programs, 1926-1941 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "Charter of the George Washington University, The", 1910-02 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "Fate of Washington's Bequest to a National University, The", 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "George Washington University", 1924 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "George Washington University, The" by Richard D. Harlan, 1909 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "George Washington University, 1821-1966, The (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "Social Register of George Washington University" Ed. Mrs. Henry Grattan Doyle, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "Statement of Facts and Objects" (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "Statement of President Needham Regarding the Plans and Work", 1909-06-21 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Stamped Cox Gift
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "University, George Washington Visualized, The", 1924 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "University Situation in Washington" by Anson Phelps Stokes, 1922-05-01 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Publications - "Washington's Bequest to a National University", 1965 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - Schools, 1910-1937 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  catalogs
- Colleges and Universities - George Wasington University - War Training Courses, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Colleges and Universities - Howard University - Howard University, 1938-1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Colleges and Universities - Miner Teachers College - Miner Teachers College, 1941-1954 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Colleges and Universities - Miner Teachers College - Publications - "Miner Fund Board of Trustees and Its Seventy-Five Years of Semi-Public Service" by William Lincoln Brown, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Cutter Number +IZN B82
- Colleges and Universities - Miner Teachers College - Publications - "Miner Normal School" (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Colleges and Universities - Miner Teachers College - Publications - "Miner Teachers College: One Hundred Years of Teacher Education, 1851-1951" (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Colleges and Universities - University of the District of Columbia - University of the District of Columbia, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Colleges and Universities - Wilson Teachers College - Wilson Teachers College, 1888-1948 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Colleges and Universities - Wood's Commercial College - Wood's Commercial College, 1893 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - Clark, Martha to Marion Ramsey - Clark, Martha to Marion Ramsey, 1864-1865 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  copies not original
- Correspondence - Copies from George Washington, Thomas Jefferson - Copies from George Washington, Thomas Jefferson, 1791-1799 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - Besoon, Josephine to Adele Parker - Besoon, Josephine to Adele Parker, 1890-09-17 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Describes her living condition in the city
- Correspondence - Durkim, F.B. to Washington Topham - Durkim, F.B. to Washington Topham, 1923-06-11 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Describes a swimming hole once located at Connecticut Avenue and DeSales Street
- Correspondence - Forrest, Joseph to Moreau Forrest - Forrest, Joseph to Moreau Forrest, 1842-11-10 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Correspondence - Kennedy, Edward M. to Hardy Franklin - Kennedy, Edward M. to Hardy Franklin, 1975-03-04 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  donation of a book to the library
- Correspondence - Luening, Otto to Ms. Dopp - Luening, Otto to Ms. Dopp, 1991-11-18 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  donation to the library
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Dupaul, F.E. to "cousin", 1908-11-20 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  about market house and market regulations
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Dupaul, Lillian to Lucien H. Stoddard, 1912-03-17 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  funeral
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Eugene to A. H. Stoddard, 1895-05-24 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  generally about the city
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Sherman, Nancy to A. H. Stoddard, 1907-12-30 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  holiday greatings
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Stoddard, C.E. to A. H. Stoddard, 1894-06-01 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Stoddard, Gene to Stoddard, 1947-02 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  partial letter
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Stoddard, Harold to L. J. Stoddard, 1909-02-21 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Taft inauguration
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Stoddard, Lauinia to Stoddard, 1907-01-07 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Stoddard, Lucien to A. H. Stoddard, 1907-01-01 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - Stoddard Family - Stoddard, Lucien to E.F. Stoddard, 1907-01-09 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Correspondence - Travel Log of Lesser Antilles by Maud Morris - Travel Log of Lesser Antilles by Maud Morris (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Crime - Publications - "Crime in the Nation's Capital, 1937", 1938-05 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Dewy Number 364.975 W32
- Crime - Publications - "District of Columbia Juvenile Delinquency Proceedings: Apprehension to Disposition", 1960 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  Published in Georgetown Law Journal
- Description of Washington DC - Clippings - Clippings, 1901-1919 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "American Mecca, The" by Edward Hungerford, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  From "Personality of American Cities," Pages 108-126
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Building of a Great Capital, The", 1900 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  From "World's Work," Pages 191-196
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Centennial of the Nation's Capital" by F. W. Fitzpatrick, 1900-12 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  Published in The Cosmopolitan pages 109-120
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Character Sketches of Cities: Washington" by Eltweed Pomeroy, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  pages 616-622
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Dining in Washington", 1961 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  small book
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "District of Columbia" (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Every-day Washington, The" by Lillian W. Betts, 1900 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - Forum Magazine, 1963-01 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Great Cities of the United States; Their Orgin and Wonderful Growth: Washington, DC" by Benson J. Lossing, 1890 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Greater Washington: The Dream of the Father of His Country and Major L'Enfant to be Realized", 1906-11 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Published in the Searchlight
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Historic Washington" by Ellen Spencer Mussey, 1912-04 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Letter XIX" by Willis Parker, 1849 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  In "Rival Letters and Other Records of Thought at Leisure"
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "National Capital, The" by F. J. Haskin, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  in "American Government"
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Nation's Capital, The" by Henry Loomis Nelson, 1898 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  Published in the Churchman
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Nation's Capital, The" by James Bryce, 1913-06 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Publiched in National Geographic Magazine
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Neighbors to the President", 2006 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "New Washington, The: The Development of the City on the Potomac into One of the World's Noblest Capitals and Finest Residential Communities" By Isaac F Marcosson, 1911-12 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  Published in Munsey's Magazine; 2 copies
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "New Washington, The" by Montgomery Schuyler, 1912-02 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Published in Scribner's Magazine; 2 copies
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Our National Capital" by Julian Ralph, 1895-04 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  Published in Harper's New Monthly Magazine
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Reminiscences of Washington", 1880 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  in complete pages from book
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Virginia Portion of the District of Columbia, The: Palisades of the Potomac" by Amos B. Casselman, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  Rocords of the Columbia Historical Society
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington", 1894 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington" by Minor Morris, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington: A City of Contrasts" by Mrs. Emily H. Randall, ca. 1900 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington, A City of Pictures" by Francis E. Leupp, 1902-02 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  Published in Scribner's Magazine, 2 copies
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington A Model City" Lt. Col. William V. Judson, 1912-04 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington: A Predestined Capital" by Anne Hillingsworth Wharton, 1901-01 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington a Representative City" by Henry S. Curtis, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington as a Spectacle", 1894-08 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  Published in the Century Magazine
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington in the New Era, 1870-1970", 1972-02 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington in Wartime; From the Journal of Ralph Waldo Emerson", 1904-07 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  Published in the Atlantic Monthly
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington Old and New" by Barry Bulkley, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  Cutter Number +F859W B87
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington, Our Capital City", 1910 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  In the Child's Book of the United States
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington Story, The" By Joseph Leeming, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington the Capital", 1913-03-03 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  The Mentor, A Wise and Faithful Guide and Friend - 2 copies
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington, The Capital of the People" by Thomas Nelson Page, 1911-03 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  in Art and Progress - 2 copies
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington: The City of Leisure", 1900 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  pages 767-778
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington, The City of Leisure" by A. Maurice Lowe, 1903-01 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  in The Bay View Magazine
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington the Incredible" by Rollin Lynde Hartt, 1917-07 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "Washington Then and Now" by Edward Everett Hale, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "White City, The" by John Moses and Paul Selby, 1893 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Our Washington: As the Artist Sees It" by J. Himmelheber, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Seeing Washington" (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Singer Souvenirs of Washington", 1939 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Souvenir of Washingon" (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Washington", 1903 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Washington" (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Washington in Miniature", 1926 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Description of Washington DC - Souvenir Books - "Washington Portfolio" by Thomas N. White (Box 17, Folder 3A)
- Description of Washington DC - Historical Tour of DC - Historical Tour of DC, ca. 1967 (Box 17, Folder 3B)
- Description of Washington DC - Publications - "New and Popular Pictorial Description of the United States", 1848 (Box 17, Folder 3C)
- Description of Washington DC - Social Statistics of Cities - Social Statistics of Cities, 1880 (Box 17, Folder 3D)
- Description of Washington DC - Transcript - "Your Washington" by Edward Boykin, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3E)
- Discrimination - Discrimination - Discrimination, 1953-09-26 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Embassies - Great Britian - Great Britian, 1904-05-04 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Ethnic Groups - Italians - Italians, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Ethnic Groups - Jewish - "Notes of Jewish Interest in the District of Columbia" by Abram Simon, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 7A)
- Ethnic Groups - Native Americans - Native Americans, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 7B)
- Events - Events - Events (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Events - Admiral Dewey Reception - Admiral Dewey Reception, 1899-10 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Events - Army and Navy Reception - Army and Navy Reception, 1907-02-07 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Events - Cherry Blossom Festival - Chery Blossom Festival, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Events - Architecture Week - Architecture Week, 2000-09 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Events - Cornwallis Surrender Celebration - Cornwallis Surrender Celebration, 1922-10-19 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  ticket
- Events - Emancipation - Emancipation, 1862-04-19 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Events - Georgetown Garden Pilgrimage - Georgetown Garden Pilgrimage, 1930-05-14 (Box 17, Folder 15A)
- Events - National Spelling Bee - National Spelling Bee (Box 17, Folder 15B)
- Events - Newbery Prize Winners Banquet, The - Newbery Prize Winners Banquet, The, 1934-11-09 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Events - Pope Francis Visit - Pope Francis Visit, 2015-09-23 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Events - Salute to Hungarians - Salute to Hungarians (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Events - Salute to Nigeria Benefit Ball - Salute to Nigeria Benefit Ball, 1960-01-15 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2000-06 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Events - Washington Youth Conference - Washington Youth Conference, 1938-11 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Events - White House Easter Egg Role - White House Easter Egg Role, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Exhibitions - Art - "Catalogue of American and Foreign Paintings and Sculpture now on Exhibition for the Benefit of the Young Men's Christian Association", 1869 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Exhibitions - Art - "Catalogue of Prof. Cromwell's Art Entertainments", 1873-01-07 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  damaged - at Willard's New Hall at Willard Hotel
- Exhibitions - Art - "Catalogue of Water Colors, by G. Bruenegh, A.R.C.A., on Exhibition at the Veerhoff Galleries", 1892-04-26 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Exhibitions - Art - Multiple, 1895 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  "Art Loan Exhibition: Washington Teachers' Bazaar" 1985-12 (damaged) and "An Exhibition of a Selection of Original Drawings by Edwin A. Abbey Illustrating Shakespeare's Comedies" 1895-12-27
- Exhibitions - Art - Multiple, 1896 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  "Exhibit of Columbia Bicycle Art Poster Designs" and "Water Colors by Paul de Longpre" 1896-02-13 thur 1896-02-25
- Exhibitions - Art - "Exhibition of the Independent Artists and Sculptors", 1927 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  1927-03-15 thru 1927-03-31 at Carlton Hotel
- Exhibitions - Art - "Carl Milles Sculpture Exhibition", 1941 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  1941-03-10 thru 1941-04-12 at Orrefors Galleries
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Exhibitions - Art - Art (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Exhibitions - Touring - "Are We to be a Nation: The Making or the Federal Constitution", 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Exhibitions - Photograph - "Our Trees and Their Woods" (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Exhibitions - Photograph - "Washington Salon and Art Photographic Exhibition of 1896" (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Camera Club of the C. Bi. C.
- Fire Department - Fire Department - Fire Department, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Fire Department - Handbook - Handbook (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Flags - Flags - Flags, 1865-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Flags - District of Columbia - "Flag for the District of Columbia, The", 1924-1968 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Flags - United States - "Rules for the Proper Uses of Heraldry in the United States", 1956-1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Funerals - Dulles, John Foster - Dulles, John Foster, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Funerals - Franklin, Hardy R. - Franklin, Hardy R., 2004-08-28 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Director of DC Public Library
- Funerals - Smyth, James A. - Smyth, James A., 1949-04-02 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Right Reverend Monsignor
- Funerals - Reagan, Ronald W. - Reagan, Ronald W., 2004-06 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  President of the United States
- Gardening - Publications - "Capital Garden and Homes", 1933 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Gardening - Publications - "Soil Management and Character of Soils in the District of Columbia" by M. S. Anderson and Walter H. Lyford, Jr., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Geology - Publications - "Geology of Washington and Vicinity" by W. J. McGee, 1891 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Halls - Convention Hall - Convention Hall, 1893-1943 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Halls - Explorers Hall - Explorers Hall (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Halls - Great Hall at the National Academy of Sciences, The - Great Hall at the National Academy of Sciences, The (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Halls - Halls of the Ancients - Halls of the Ancients, 1900-1904 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Health - Diseases - Diseases (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Hospitals - Children's Hospital - Children's Hospital (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Hospitals - Children's Hospital - Report of Special Committee, Defining Duties of House Physician and Matron, and Establishing a System of Weekly Inspections", 1882 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Hospitals - Cholera Hospital - Cholera Hospital, 1822 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Hospitals - Columbia Hospital for Women - Columbia Hospital for Women, 1882-1966 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Hospitals - Columbia Hospital for Women - "Charter, By-Laws of the Columbia Hospital for Women and Lying-in Asylum", 1866 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Hospitals - Columbia Hospital for Women - "Columbia Hospital and Lying-in Asylum, A Government Institution, Its Past and Present Management" by a Citizen of Washington, D.C., 1877 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Hospitals - Columbia Hospital for Women - "Charter Statutes By-Laws and Regulations of the Columbia Hospital for Women and Lying-in Asylum", 1902-01 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Hospitals - DC General - DC General, 1955-1956 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Hospitals - Freedman's Hospitals - Freedman's Hospitals, 1939-1949 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Hospitals - Garfield Memorial Hospital - Garfield Memorial Hospital (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Hospitals - George Washington University Hospital - "A Garden Party on the Potomac", 1928-02-21 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Hospitals - Municipal Hospital of DC - "Programme of Competition for a Municipal Hospital for the District of Columbia", 1902 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Hospitals - Naval Hospital - Naval Hospital, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Hospitals - Providence Hospital - Providence Hospital (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Manuscript material
- Hospitals - Walter Reed - Walter Reed, 1919-1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Hospitals - Washington Asylum - "Report of the Commissioners of the Washington Asylum", 1862-1863 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Hospitals - Washington Clinic - "The Washington Clinic", 1955 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Hospitals - Washington Infimary - Washington Infimary, ca. 1858 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Hotels - Brown's Indian Queen Hotel - Brown's Indian Queen Hotel, 1834 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Hotels - Hotels - Hotels (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Hotels - Brown's Marble Hotel - Brown's Marble Hotel, 1855 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Hotels - Burlington Hotel - Burlington Hotel (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Hotels - Cairo Hotel - Cairo Hotel (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Hotels - Carlton Hotel - Carlton Hotel (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Hotels - Carroll Arms, The - Carroll Arms, The (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Hotels - Cavalier Hotel - Cavalier Hotel (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Hotels - Congressional Hotel - Congressional Hotel (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Hotels - Grace Dodge Hotel - Grace Dodge Hotel, ca. 1938 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Hotels - Hotel Commodore - Hotel Commodore (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Hotels - Hotel Continental - Hotel Continental (Box 19, Folder 21)
  Cox Gift
- Hotels - Mayflower, The - Mayflower, The (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Hotels - National Hotel - National Hotel, 1835-1914 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Hotels - Normandie Manor - Normandie Manor (Box 19, Folder 24)